ski-lifts.com 2018-09-25

# Privacy Policy | Ski-Lifts

* * *

At Ski-Lifts, we are committed to protecting your privacy and take the responsibility regarding the security of our customers’ information very seriously. Please read the following for details of our privacy policy.

 **About Us**

This is a privacy policy for Ski-Lifts Ltd.

Ski-Lifts Ltd is a UK based booking agent, whose registered company number is 05342964 and whose registered address is – Suite 1.2, Canada House, 3 Chepstow Street, Manchester, M1 5FW, United Kingdom.

Our homepage is located at [https://www.ski-lifts.com](https://www.ski-lifts.com/).

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:  
Suite 1.2  
Canada House  
3 Chepstow Street  
Manchester  
M1 5FW  
United Kingdom

You may contact us by e-mail at [info@ski-lifts.com](mailto:info@ski-lifts.com). You may call us at +442088197950.

 **Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals**

If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way then please email [info@ski-lifts.com](mailto:info@ski-lifts.com) and we will resolve your concern.

* * *

1\. What information do we collect and how do we use it?  
2\. Who do we share your information with?  
3\. Security and data protection requirements  
5\. Cookies  
6\. Your consent  
7\. Marketing communications  
8\. Rights of access to your personal information

## 1\. What information do we collect and how do we use it?

In order to process your booking, we do require certain information. This will include the name of the person making the booking, billing address, mobile telephone number, email address, and your credit card details. We also need to establish your flight details, destination resort and accommodation. All of this information is collated, used and stored for different reasons, as shown below:

 ** _Your name, email address, mobile number_**

 **How we use these details**|  **Why?**  
---|---  
Book and arrange your transfer| We need these details to perform our contract with you, and in case we need to get in contact with you regarding your order.  
Send you service messages and updates about your transfer via email and text| We must send you a confirmation email as part of our contract with you. We may need to send you updates about your transfer, to connect you with your driver and help with your trip, particularly in the unlikely event of changes to any part of your journey.  
Send you information and offers by email| We like to offer our email subscribers exclusive offers and deals, as well as updates on our products and services – but only with your permission.  
  
 ** _Your travel, flight and accommodation details_**

 **How we use these details**|  **Why?**  
---|---  
Send your flight and accommodation details to our suppliers| We do this so the supplier can track your arrival or departure times and ensure your transfer is as smooth and timely as possible. Your supplier also needs to know where to drop you off and pick you up.  
  
 ** _Your payment & billing details_**

 **How we use these details**|  **Why?**  
---|---  
Take, or refund, payments| All our websites’ financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Paypal. You should only provide your personal information to Paypal after reviewing the Paypal privacy policy (available at www.paypal.com).  
  
 ** _Your responses to surveys and competitions on social media and our blogs_**

 **How we use these details**|  **Why?**  
---|---  
Run surveys and competitions| We run these in order to obtain useful information about our website and service as well as helping us spread the word about Ski-Lifts! Any personal data entered is used only as stated – either permission to send you emails or for one-time use in draws after which any personal details will be deleted after 30 days.  
  
 ** _Your contact and purchase history with us_**

 **How we use these details**|  **Why?**  
---|---  
Use your contact history for customer support| Your contact history with us is necessary to perform our contract with you, as well as helping our customer support staff assist you with your purchases and travel.  
Use your purchase history for customer support| Your purchase history with us is necessary to perform our contract with you, as well as helping our customer support staff assist you with your purchases and travel, and ensuring that any email offers you have asked to be sent are as relevant as possible.  
  
 ** _Information about your mobile device or computer when you visit our website_**

 **How we use these details**|  **Why?**  
---|---  
Learn about our users and customers, improve our website and set appropriate options such as currency and language| We want to give our website visitors the best possible experience, so we use software or tools such as Google Analytics to help us improve our website, apps and any other touchpoints with you, whether through the website or via our various customer support services. This data is always anonymised and aggregated.  
  
## 2\. Who do we share your information with?

Ski-Lifts never shares your payment details with anyone. We collate – but do not store – your payment information solely for the purpose of making your booking. If you have booked via a Ski-Lifts affiliate site, then the affiliate has the right to request and receive your booking data, but not your payment data.

 **Reviews**

We send your trip and contact information to our review platform, TrustPilot, from which emails will be sent to request a review for your purchase or journey. This data is ONLY used for the purposes of these review request emails and nothing else. We may also ask our customers to post reviews on other platforms such as Facebook Reviews and Google Reviews but these do not involve the sharing of any contact or transaction details.

 **Suppliers**

The only companies we share some of your information with are the suppliers involved with your transfer, and they will use the minimum information ONLY for communications with you for that transfer. By using the website, you consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (where the service you book requires a non-EEA supplier to provide it).

 **Advertising**

Your browsing data may be shared with other advertising or affiliate partners who help us promote our business, but any data is anonymous and aggregated.

 **Affiliates**

If you have booked via a Ski-Lifts affiliate website, then the affiliate has the right to request and receive your booking data, but not your payment data.

 **Other websites**

There are several places on the Ski-Lifts website where we link through to other websites. Once you click through onto another site, Ski-Lifts privacy practices no longer apply. We recommend you view privacy statements for all third-party websites to understand their own policies for collecting and disclosing your information.

## 3\. Security and data protection requirements

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2016 which superseded it in May 2018, we are a data controller. In order to process your booking, we need to collect certain personal details from you. These will include, where applicable, the names and addresses of the party’s members, credit/debit card or other payment details and special requirements such as those relating to any disability or medical condition which may affect the chosen booking.

If we need any other personal details, we will tell you before we obtain them from you. In order to process your order, we may share your information with our supplier(s) or other involved third parties. We will provide only the personally identifiable information necessary to ensure the successful fulfilment of your travel arrangements.

We have appropriate security measures in place to protect the personal details you give us. We will not pass any information on to any company and/or organisation not responsible for providing any part of your travel arrangements. Where you provide us with personal details relating to any special requirements and/or details of any illnesses, disabilities or religious requirements, you consent to this information being passed onto any organisation or companies responsible for any part of your travel arrangements whether in the EEA or not. If we cannot pass this information to the relevant suppliers, we cannot process your booking.

We are entitled to assume you do not object to our doing any of the things mentioned above unless you tell us otherwise in writing. You are generally entitled to ask us (by letter or email) what details of yours are being held or processed, for what purpose and to whom they may be or have been disclosed. We will charge a fee to respond to such a request. Please email us at [info@ski-lifts.com](mailto:info@ski-lifts.com). In limited circumstances, we are entitled to refuse your request. Except where expressly permitted by the General Data Protection Regulation, we will only deal with the personal details you give us as set out above unless you agree otherwise.

## 4\. Children and privacy

If you’re aged under 18, you cannot make any bookings on our website – a parent, guardian or appropriate adult must book on your behalf.

## 5\. Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Cookies can be deleted from your hard drive if you wish. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features on the website. For more information, please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.ski-lifts.com/our-cookie-policy/) page.

## 6\. Your consent

By using the Ski-Lifts website and our affiliate sites, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Ski-Lifts in the ways outlined above. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it and in what circumstances we disclose it.

## 7\. Marketing communications

We would like to hold your information (including email address and phone number(s)) for Ski-Lifts marketing purposes. You will be asked for your consent before any marketing takes place, and if specific consent is granted we may use your personal information to contact you by email, telephone, SMS, social media, electronic messaging or post – with information and/or offers on products, services, discounts or promotions (provided by us) that we think may be of interest to you. For marketing purposes, your information will be stored in our email database. At any point, you can refuse or opt out of marketing messages by simply clicking UNSUBSCRIBE on any of our emails, or contacting our Customer Support team at [info@ski-lifts.com](mailto:info@ski-lifts.com). This does not include our automated pre-departure and post-departure emails and SMS messages, which are service-related and will help you with your trip).

Ski-Lifts have many trade partners who from time to time give us access to offers and promotions they may have running, allowing you to become one of the first to be notified of any great travel bargains. Where you’ve given us your permission to send you marketing emails, you give us prior authorisation to email these offers by registering on the website and can, of course, opt out by unsubscribing at any time.

## 8\. Rights of access to your personal information

We only store the minimum possible amount of personal information, which is required to process your booking and for contractual reasons.

At any time, you have a right to request access to the data we hold about you, which we will provide free of charge within 30 days unless requests are repetitive and excessive in which case we may charge a small administration fee. You have a right to update or delete your personal data. Of course, you have a right to unsubscribe from our marketing emails at any time by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in all of our emails, which will remove you from our mailing lists immediately.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

This policy is dated 20th May 2018. We may change and improve this from time to time, at which point we will update the policy with the appropriate date.
